<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog | Cringe Lord</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_645fa481986063ef.png</url>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Your Own PC: A Journey of Hope and Regret</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/pc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;building-your-own-pc-a-journey-of-hope-and-regret&#34;&gt;Building Your Own PC: A Journey of Hope and Regret&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, you’ve decided to build your own PC? Bold move. You could have just bought a pre-built machine, but no—you&amp;rsquo;re an &lt;em&gt;engineer&lt;/em&gt;, a &lt;em&gt;technologist&lt;/em&gt;, a &lt;em&gt;visionary&lt;/em&gt;! You refuse to be scammed by overpriced &amp;ldquo;gaming&amp;rdquo; setups with RGB everything. Instead, you’ll venture into the dangerous world of DIY computer assembly, armed with only a screwdriver and a growing sense of regret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s break down the &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; process of building a PC—step by step, mistake by mistake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1-the-shopping-spree&#34;&gt;Step 1: The Shopping Spree&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, you’ll spend &lt;em&gt;weeks&lt;/em&gt; researching components, watching endless YouTube videos, and reading forum arguments about AMD vs. Intel. Eventually, you’ll settle on your parts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🧠 &lt;strong&gt;CPU&lt;/strong&gt; – The brain of your PC. Pick one that&amp;rsquo;s powerful enough but not &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; powerful, or else you’ll spend the next five years saving for a compatible GPU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🎨 &lt;strong&gt;GPU&lt;/strong&gt; – The most expensive part, because &lt;em&gt;of course&lt;/em&gt; you want to play games at ultra settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💾 &lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; – More is better, unless you enjoy watching Chrome devour your entire system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;📦 &lt;strong&gt;Motherboard&lt;/strong&gt; – Good luck picking the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; one. It must support your CPU, your RAM, your GPU, your hopes, and your dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🔌 &lt;strong&gt;Power Supply (PSU)&lt;/strong&gt; – The most overlooked part. Get a good one unless you want to &lt;em&gt;literally&lt;/em&gt; set your house on fire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💨 &lt;strong&gt;Cooling&lt;/strong&gt; – Air cooling? Liquid cooling? Stock cooler? Whatever you choose, remember: overheating is just your PC telling you it’s &lt;em&gt;too powerful&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-2-the-assembly-aka-the-panic-phase&#34;&gt;Step 2: The Assembly (a.k.a. The Panic Phase)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that you have your parts, it’s time for the fun part—putting them together! Here’s how it usually goes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Place the motherboard&lt;/strong&gt; in the case. Realize you forgot to install the I/O shield. Remove everything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install the CPU&lt;/strong&gt;. Carefully. Like, &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; carefully. Drop it once and congratulations—you now own a very expensive paperweight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply thermal paste&lt;/strong&gt;. Too little? Your CPU melts. Too much? Your entire motherboard turns into a disaster zone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install RAM&lt;/strong&gt;. Try forcing it in the wrong way for 15 minutes before realizing it only fits &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect the power cables&lt;/strong&gt;. Spend half an hour searching for where they actually go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turn it on&lt;/strong&gt;. Nothing happens. Cry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-3-the-debugging-ritual&#34;&gt;Step 3: The Debugging Ritual&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your PC refuses to turn on. Fantastic. Time for &lt;strong&gt;troubleshooting&lt;/strong&gt;, also known as &lt;em&gt;guessing until it works&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the &lt;strong&gt;RAM seated properly&lt;/strong&gt;? (Spoiler: It never is.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did you &lt;strong&gt;plug in the CPU power cable&lt;/strong&gt;? No? Fix that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there &lt;strong&gt;a rogue standoff&lt;/strong&gt; shorting your motherboard? Better hope not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you tried &lt;strong&gt;turning it off and on again&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still nothing? Welcome to the BIOS, where settings make no sense and the interface looks like it was designed in 1998.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-4-victory-or-defeat&#34;&gt;Step 4: Victory (Or Defeat)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, through sheer luck and stubbornness, your PC boots up. You let out a sigh of relief, install your OS, and finally experience the joy of a working system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least until a &lt;strong&gt;random blue screen&lt;/strong&gt; ruins your day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But hey, congratulations! You’re now part of an elite group of PC builders—those who have suffered through the process, made every mistake possible, and somehow emerged victorious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now go enjoy your &lt;em&gt;perfectly optimized&lt;/em&gt; gaming rig. Until, of course, next year, when you convince yourself you need an upgrade. 🚀💻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💡 &lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Take a picture of your perfectly built PC. It’ll remind you why you should &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; do this again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Life of a Web Developer: A Tale of Code and Existential Dread</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/fin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/fin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-life-of-a-web-developer-a-tale-of-code-and-existential-dread&#34;&gt;The Life of a Web Developer: A Tale of Code and Existential Dread&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-beginning-a-dream-and-a-javascript-tutorial&#34;&gt;The Beginning: A Dream and a JavaScript Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, I thought being a web developer was about &lt;em&gt;creating beautiful things&lt;/em&gt;. I imagined sleek interfaces, smooth animations, and users who would admire my craftsmanship. So, with hope in my heart, I opened my first HTML file, added a &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, and felt like a digital Michelangelo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then I met &lt;strong&gt;CSS&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah, CSS—the art of telling a box where to go, only for it to disobey you like a rebellious teenager. I quickly learned that getting a button to sit &lt;em&gt;exactly&lt;/em&gt; where you want it is less about logic and more about bargaining with unknown forces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then came &lt;strong&gt;JavaScript&lt;/strong&gt;. A language so powerful it can do &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;, but so chaotic it can also ruin your entire afternoon because of a missing semicolon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And thus, my journey began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-middle-an-endless-cycle-of-hope-and-despair&#34;&gt;The Middle: An Endless Cycle of Hope and Despair&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a web developer is like playing an infinite game of Jenga. You build things, stack features on top of each other, and pray nothing collapses. Some key experiences along the way:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-framework-fomo&#34;&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Framework FOMO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every six months, a new JavaScript framework emerges, and suddenly, you’re outdated. Remember when React was &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; thing? Now it’s all about Svelte. Or is it Solid? Or maybe it’s time to go back to plain HTML for “simplicity”? Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-the-great-backend-awakening&#34;&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;The Great Backend Awakening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first, I thought I could just be a front-end developer. But then someone asked, &lt;em&gt;“Can you set up an API?”&lt;/em&gt; and just like that, I was dragged into the world of databases, authentication, and error messages that made me question my entire existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-the-deployment-crisis&#34;&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;The Deployment Crisis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Works on my machine” is the mantra of every developer who has ever deployed a project only for it to fail &lt;strong&gt;spectacularly&lt;/strong&gt; in production. Debugging a live website at 3 AM while whispering &lt;em&gt;“please just work”&lt;/em&gt; is a rite of passage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-present-acceptance-or-something-like-it&#34;&gt;The Present: Acceptance (Or Something Like It)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After years of battling CSS grids, deciphering cryptic error messages, and rewriting the same app in three different frameworks, I’ve reached a conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Web development is not about perfection. It’s about &lt;em&gt;survival&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will never write &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; perfect code. You will never master &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the tools. There will always be a bug that refuses to die and a client who asks, &lt;em&gt;“Can we make the logo bigger?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And yet, somehow, we keep going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because in between the headaches, there’s &lt;strong&gt;the thrill of solving a problem&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;the joy of seeing your work come to life&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;the satisfaction of knowing that, despite the chaos, you built something real&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if that “something” is just another to-do app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-future-who-knows&#34;&gt;The Future: Who Knows?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will AI replace us? Will the web be completely rewritten in WebAssembly? Will I finally understand CSS Flexbox?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for now, I’ll keep writing code, fixing bugs, and pretending I know what I’m doing—just like every other developer out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💡 &lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; If your website isn’t working, just clear the cache. Or restart your computer. Or switch careers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🤓 Scientific Programming Languages. The Art of Making Your Brain Hurt</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/proglangs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/proglangs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;scientific-programming-languages-the-art-of-making-your-brain-hurt&#34;&gt;Scientific Programming Languages: The Art of Making Your Brain Hurt&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, you’ve decided to enter the glorious world of scientific programming? Congratulations! You are now on the path of endless debugging, cryptic error messages, and wondering why your code works perfectly on your machine but collapses into chaos on the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But before you start your descent into madness, you need to choose your weapon—uh, I mean, your programming language. So, let’s take a look at the fine selection of scientific programming tools available to us, and why each one is both a blessing and a curse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-usual-suspects&#34;&gt;The Usual Suspects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-python-the-king-of-convenience&#34;&gt;🐍 Python: The King of Convenience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python is the undisputed champion of scientific computing. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to read, has more libraries than you’ll ever use, and runs (eventually).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✅ &lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can do &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; in Python: data analysis, simulations, machine learning, summoning eldritch horrors from NumPy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jupyter notebooks make you feel like a real scientist (until you accidentally run a cell twice and ruin your whole dataset).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The community is massive—if you have a problem, someone has probably already solved it on Stack Overflow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;❌ &lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speed? What’s that? Python laughs in the face of performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependency hell. Installing the right versions of NumPy, SciPy, and Matplotlib is an art form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing parallelized code? Prepare to meet the GIL (Global Interpreter Lock), your new worst enemy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-matlab-the-expensive-spreadsheet&#34;&gt;🧮 MATLAB: The Expensive Spreadsheet&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATLAB is what happens when scientists need to code but don’t want to &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✅ &lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matrix operations feel like magic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great plotting capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used by every engineering department, so you &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; learn it at some point.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;❌ &lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Costs more than your soul.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory management? Never heard of it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your research group makes you use MATLAB, it’s probably because their 15-year-old scripts still work (barely).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-fortran-the-ancient-one&#34;&gt;👴 Fortran: The Ancient One&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortran has been around longer than most of us, and it still refuses to die. Scientists love it because it &lt;em&gt;works&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✅ &lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazing fast. Faster than C in some cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still heavily used in physics and numerical simulations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;❌ &lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feels like programming in a haunted house—every change risks waking up a ghost from the 1970s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good luck finding modern documentation that doesn’t look like it was typed on a typewriter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People will judge you (but secretly respect you).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;honorable-mentions&#34;&gt;Honorable Mentions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R&lt;/strong&gt; – For people who love statistics and pain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julia&lt;/strong&gt; – Python, but &lt;em&gt;faster&lt;/em&gt; (in theory).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C++&lt;/strong&gt; – When Python isn’t suffering enough for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wolfram Mathematica&lt;/strong&gt; – Because why not turn math into dark magic?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choosing a scientific programming language is like choosing your favorite method of self-inflicted torment. No matter which one you pick, you will spend hours debugging, rewriting, and questioning your life choices. But in the end, the true scientific method is about suffering &lt;em&gt;efficiently&lt;/em&gt;, and that’s what these languages are here for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now go forth and code! Or stare at a segmentation fault for the next five hours. Either way, you’re doing science. 🔬🚀&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🥱 Life is boring</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/bored/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/bored/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fatigue-of-doing-absolutely-nothing&#34;&gt;The Fatigue of Doing Absolutely Nothing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It happened. A historical event, a paradox, an enigma wrapped in mystery—call it what you want, but here I am, completely exhausted… from doing absolutely nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Day in, day out, I sit in my cozy cave, rarely stepping outside, except for the occasional quest to the refrigerator or the ritualistic pacing around the room while pretending to be productive. And yet, somehow, despite moving less than a houseplant, I feel drained. Physically, mentally, spiritually. Even my shadow looks disappointed in me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-science-behind-the-mystery&#34;&gt;The Science Behind the Mystery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experts would say, “You’re just mentally exhausted,” or perhaps something even more sophisticated like “prolonged sensory deprivation can lead to fatigue.” Yeah, sure. But explain to me why my biggest physical exertion this week was reaching for my phone that fell under the bed, and I still feel like I just ran a marathon—backwards, uphill, in the snow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The symptoms?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sudden inability to focus (which, to be fair, has always been my superpower).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The feeling of wanting to do something but not knowing what (classic).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The crushing realization that I could, theoretically, go outside… but the mere thought of putting on shoes is exhausting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;solutions-that-will-probably-not-work&#34;&gt;Solutions That Will Probably Not Work&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, every self-help guru and motivational coach would have solutions:&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Take a walk.&lt;/strong&gt; (I walked to the kitchen. Didn&amp;rsquo;t help.)&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Exercise.&lt;/strong&gt; (I opened a fitness app, looked at it, then closed it. Didn&amp;rsquo;t help.)&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Meditate.&lt;/strong&gt; (I tried staring at a wall for 10 minutes. Didn&amp;rsquo;t help. Also, boring.)&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Get some sunlight.&lt;/strong&gt; (There’s a window. That counts, right?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-inevitable-conclusion&#34;&gt;The Inevitable Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth is, doing nothing is actually really tiring. A body at rest, it turns out, does not stay at rest—it dissolves into a sluggish, existentially confused entity questioning its very purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will I recover? Probably. Will I change anything about my routine? Unlikely. But for now, I will embrace this state of paradoxical exhaustion, stare at the ceiling for an undetermined amount of time, and then, with great effort, return to my primary occupation&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>📜 The Art of Report Writing in Markdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-art-of-report-writing-in-markdown&#34;&gt;The Art of Report Writing in Markdown&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations! You’ve been tasked with writing a report. Maybe it’s for work, maybe for university, or maybe just to convince yourself that Markdown is superior to everything else. Either way, you need something structured, readable, and, most importantly, NOT in Word. That’s where Markdown comes in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown allows you to format reports with minimal effort while keeping things clean and distraction-free. Let’s explore how to make your reports both professional and a tiny bit chaotic (just like your thought process).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sections--headings&#34;&gt;Sections &amp;amp; Headings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every serious report needs structure. In Markdown, you do this with &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; for headings. The bigger the heading, the fewer &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; symbols:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;gh&#34;&gt;# Big Important Title
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;gh&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;gu&#34;&gt;## Slightly Less Important Section
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;gu&#34;&gt;### Minor Detail You’ll Probably Skip
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your reader’s patience decreases with every &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; you add, so use them wisely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lists-because-bullet-points-look-smart&#34;&gt;Lists: Because Bullet Points Look Smart&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don’t want to write long paragraphs (who does?), you can summarize everything in lists:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Key findings: People don&amp;#39;t read documentation.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Solution: Write shorter reports.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Conclusion: Markdown saves lives.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the truly ambitious:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;1.&lt;/span&gt; Pretend to research.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;2.&lt;/span&gt; Write down conclusions before actually researching.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;3.&lt;/span&gt; Add footnotes to look credible.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;4.&lt;/span&gt; Profit.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;tables-the-excel-killer-almost&#34;&gt;Tables: The Excel Killer (Almost)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your boss/professor loves tables. Markdown provides a way to make them without pulling your hair out:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;| Feature        | Word        | Markdown |
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;|---------------|------------|----------|
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;| Formatting    | Painful    | Effortless |
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;| File Size     | 50MB+      | 5KB       |
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;| Sanity Level  | Dropping   | Maintained |
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’re welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blockquotes-sound-more-important-than-you-are&#34;&gt;Blockquotes: Sound More Important Than You Are&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;&amp;gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;ge&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Good documentation is written, not found.&amp;#34; — Some Wise Person
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use this when you want to appear deep and intellectual without actually doing extra work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-blocks-for-when-you-want-to-show-off&#34;&gt;Code Blocks: For When You Want to Show Off&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;print(&amp;ldquo;Hello, Markdown report!&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-fallback&#34; data-lang=&#34;fallback&#34;&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is crucial if your report involves coding or if you just want to flex your ability to write three lines of Python.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;footnotes-make-people-think-you-did-research&#34;&gt;Footnotes: Make People Think You Did Research&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;Markdown is great[^1].
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;[^1]: Source: Trust me, bro.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;exporting-your-report-good-luck&#34;&gt;Exporting Your Report (Good Luck!)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is simple, but if you need a polished PDF, you’ll need Pandoc, LaTeX, and possibly a few hours of suffering:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-sh&#34; data-lang=&#34;sh&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;pandoc report.md -o report.pdf
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or you can just keep it as Markdown and pretend it’s meant to be “raw and minimalistic.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing reports in Markdown is easy, fun, and much less frustrating than using Word. Plus, you can pretend you’re a hacker while formatting your text. Just remember: &lt;strong&gt;less is more&lt;/strong&gt;, except when it comes to procrastination.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Majestic Solitude of a Hilltop Toilet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/toilet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/toilet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-majestic-solitude-of-a-hilltop-toilet&#34;&gt;The Majestic Solitude of a Hilltop Toilet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It all started with innocent procrastination. You know, the usual routine: opening a meme page for &amp;lsquo;just five minutes&amp;rsquo; and resurfacing hours later with an existential crisis. But this time, something was different. Amidst the sea of cat gifs and vintage reaction images, I stumbled upon &lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;—a breathtaking photograph of a lonely toilet, nobly perched atop a hill, surveying the boundless horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A toilet. On a hill. Alone. &lt;strong&gt;Majestic.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-philosophical-implications-of-an-elevated-restroom&#34;&gt;The Philosophical Implications of an Elevated Restroom&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first, I laughed. Then, I stared. And then—like a true connoisseur of internet-induced epiphanies—I began to &lt;em&gt;think.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this not the pinnacle of human existence?&lt;/strong&gt; A structure built with purpose, now transcending mere functionality to embody the ultimate metaphor for life’s solitude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does the toilet feel lonely?&lt;/strong&gt; Does it long for visitors, or has it embraced its isolation, content with its panoramic view?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this, in fact, the perfect toilet?&lt;/strong&gt; Free from the judgmental gaze of society, blessed with fresh air and an uninterrupted landscape.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-work-of-art-a-monument-to-resilience&#34;&gt;A Work of Art, A Monument to Resilience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One can only imagine the journey of the person who built this masterpiece. Did they dream of a world where nature and necessity coexisted in harmony? Were they a misunderstood visionary, mocked by their peers, yet steadfast in their quest to merge sanitation with scenery?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps this toilet is not just an object, but a &lt;strong&gt;statement&lt;/strong&gt;—a testament to the perseverance of those who refuse to accept limitations, who boldly ask, &lt;em&gt;“Why not here?”&lt;/em&gt; instead of &lt;em&gt;“Why here?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-takeaway-procrastination-is-a-gateway-to-enlightenment&#34;&gt;The Takeaway: Procrastination is a Gateway to Enlightenment&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would I have discovered this profound insight had I not spent an irresponsible amount of time scrolling through internet nonsense? Absolutely not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, let this be a lesson to us all: sometimes, the best way to reflect on life is to let your mind wander aimlessly. Who knows? You, too, may one day stumble upon an image so powerful, so unexpected, that it reshapes your entire understanding of the universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if not, well, at least you’ve seen a toilet on a hill. That’s still pretty great.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🌀 Versioning as an Art. The Journey of Alexander Mazursky</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/git/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alexander Mazursky, a man who has survived thousands of commits, knows firsthand what it’s like to lose code after two days of hard work. That’s why he decided to share his thoughts on Git and version control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-git&#34;&gt;Why Git?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Git is not just a version control system; it’s your safety net against disasters. Imagine this: you&amp;rsquo;re crafting a genius piece of code, but then you decide to &amp;ldquo;improve&amp;rdquo; it, and suddenly it stops working. What do you do? Git lets you roll back in time as if you hacked the timeline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;essential-commands&#34;&gt;Essential Commands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s a short list of commands that have saved thousands of developers from nervous breakdowns:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git init   &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Create a repository&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git add .  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Stage changes&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git commit -m &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Masterpiece saved&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Commit changes&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git push   &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Push to a remote repository&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git pull   &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Fetch changes from the server&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git reset --hard HEAD~1  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Revert the last changes&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;branching-and-merging&#34;&gt;Branching and Merging&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Git allows you to create parallel realities in your code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git branch feature_x  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Create a new branch&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git checkout feature_x  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Switch to it&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;git merge main  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;# Merge changes&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Git is not just a tool; it’s a philosophy. Use it wisely, and your code will be safe. And if not—just run &lt;code&gt;git blame&lt;/code&gt; and find the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;found-this-helpful-share-it-with-your-friends-&#34;&gt;Found this helpful? Share it with your friends! 🚀&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🥶 Markdown The Great and Terrible</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/markdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;markdown-the-great-and-terrible&#34;&gt;Markdown: The Great and Terrible&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever written text in &lt;code&gt;.txt&lt;/code&gt; files but dreamed of it looking like in Word, without weighing 100 MB and opening for half an hour — congratulations, Markdown was made for you! This magical markup turns dull plain text into structured, readable, and (almost) beautiful text. All of this without the need to learn the esoteric symbols of HTML or consult with LaTeX priests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;basics-how-to-break-text-with-minimal-effort&#34;&gt;Basics: &lt;strong&gt;How to break text with minimal effort&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown allows you to do the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Headings&lt;/strong&gt; — just put &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; before the text. The more &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt;, the lower the heading level. Only the bravest and most lost souls venture deeper than the third level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bold and italic text&lt;/strong&gt; — use &lt;code&gt;**asterisks**&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;_underscores_&lt;/code&gt;. But be careful: too much formatting, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be mistaken for a frontend developer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lists&lt;/strong&gt; — use &lt;code&gt;-&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;*&lt;/code&gt;. If you want an ordered list, use &lt;code&gt;1.&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;2.&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;3.&lt;/code&gt;, and enjoy the sense of control over chaos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links&lt;/strong&gt; — &lt;code&gt;[Click here](https://example.com)&lt;/code&gt;. Perfect for luring unsuspecting users to your page with 2012 memes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Code&lt;/strong&gt; — Wrap text in backticks `code`, or triple backticks ``` if you want to show off a lengthy SQL query.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-markdown-is-your-new-best-friend&#34;&gt;Why Markdown is your new best friend&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is simple, like a bicycle without wheels. It allows you to focus on content, not formatting, and it also:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✅ Is supported everywhere: from GitHub to Telegram. Even grandma’s recipes can now be marked up in &lt;code&gt;.md&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
✅ Is great for documentation if you like writing it (but, let’s be honest, you probably don’t).&lt;br&gt;
✅ Supports HTML, so if you want to add &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;blink&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, no one will stop you.
✅ Supports LaTeX, so if you want to make your article impenetrable to 99% of readers, you can insert formulas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-dark-side-of-markdown&#34;&gt;The dark side of Markdown&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But not everything is so rosy. There are problems:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;❌ If you need a complex layout… forget it. Want tables? Enjoy the pain with &lt;code&gt;|&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;---&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
❌ Support across different platforms is inconsistent. Sometimes links work, sometimes they don’t. And sometimes, lists turn into chaos.&lt;br&gt;
❌ Importing into Word or Google Docs is a quest worthy of its own survival horror game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is like minimalism in programming: if you don’t need anything extra, it’s the perfect tool. But if you need complex formatting, either you’re in the wrong place or you haven’t gone through the denial stage yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use Markdown responsibly, and perhaps one day your README files will not only be useful but also readable. Although, to be honest, that’s probably unlikely.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🧠 The Cringe Lord&#39;s Quirky Encounter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/enigmatic-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/enigmatic-horse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mazursky Alexander, a.k.a. Cringe Lord (formerly known as Embarassment Seignour), once again embarked on an epic digital odyssey. Amid an endless scroll of memes and bizarre content, his tired eyes caught sight of something that defied explanation—a photograph so absurd it could only be described as a masterpiece of online oddity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A humanized horse in a suit. Not just any horse—a dignified equine figure seated pensively atop a perfectly round object, its shape suspiciously reminiscent of a certain delicate anatomical feature. To add to the enigma, the image boldly displayed the cryptic inscription &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;в 13:57&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;, as if marking this surreal moment in time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-encounter&#34;&gt;The Encounter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Armed with relentless curiosity and a flair for the bizarre, Mazursky dove deep into the internet&amp;rsquo;s underbelly. In a realm where the mundane meets the surreal, this discovery was nothing short of a revelation—a rare gem proving that the digital world&amp;rsquo;s creative spirit knows no bounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mindmaps-of-madness&#34;&gt;Mindmaps of Madness&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To truly process the significance of his find, Mazursky did what any self-respecting digital archivist would do—he crafted a mindmap. Because if a humanized horse in a suit with such absurd gravity is to be celebrated, it deserves to be documented in exquisite detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
```markmap {height=&#34;200px&#34;}
- The Enigmatic Horse
  - Encountered by Cringe Lord
  - Significance
    - **Meme potential**: Infinite
    - ~~Realism~~: Overrated
    - Intrigue level: Off the charts
```
&lt;/code&gt; 
&lt;/pre&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;renders as&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;markmap&#34; style=&#34;height: 200px;&#34;&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;- The Enigmatic Horse
  - Encountered by Cringe Lord
  - Significance
    - **Meme potential**: Infinite
    - ~~Realism~~: Overrated
    - Intrigue level: Off the charts&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-art-of-highlighting&#34;&gt;The Art of Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark&gt;This horse is no ordinary steed.&lt;/mark&gt; It stands as an icon of digital absurdity, a testament to the internet&amp;rsquo;s unyielding creativity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;mark&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Behold, the enigmatic horse in all its quirky glory.&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;mark&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-call-to-action&#34;&gt;A Call to Action&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use callouts to ensure the weight of this discovery is never forgotten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% callout note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;This humanized horse might just redefine the boundaries of internet humor.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% /callout %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;renders as&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;flex px-4 py-3 mb-6 rounded-md bg-primary-100 dark:bg-primary-900&#34;&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;pr-3 pt-1 text-primary-600 dark:text-primary-300&#34;&gt;
  &lt;svg height=&#34;24&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&gt;&lt;path fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34; stroke-width=&#34;1.5&#34; d=&#34;m11.25 11.25l.041-.02a.75.75 0 0 1 1.063.852l-.708 2.836a.75.75 0 0 0 1.063.853l.041-.021M21 12a9 9 0 1 1-18 0a9 9 0 0 1 18 0m-9-3.75h.008v.008H12z&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;dark:text-neutral-300&#34;&gt;This humanized horse might just redefine the boundaries of internet humor.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, to truly emphasize the gravity of this revelation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;flex px-4 py-3 mb-6 rounded-md bg-yellow-100 dark:bg-yellow-900&#34;&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;pr-3 pt-1 text-red-400&#34;&gt;
  &lt;svg height=&#34;24&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&gt;&lt;path fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34; stroke-width=&#34;1.5&#34; d=&#34;M12 9v3.75m-9.303 3.376c-.866 1.5.217 3.374 1.948 3.374h14.71c1.73 0 2.813-1.874 1.948-3.374L13.949 3.378c-.866-1.5-3.032-1.5-3.898 0zM12 15.75h.007v.008H12z&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;dark:text-neutral-300&#34;&gt;Viewer discretion is advised: this image is not for the faint-hearted.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-find-this-page-helpful-consider-sharing-it--or-even-betterspread-the-legend-of-the-enigmatic-horse-&#34;&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌 Or, even better—spread the legend of the enigmatic horse! 🐴✨&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🧠 The Cringe Lord&#39;s Greatest Discovery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-performance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mazursky Alexander a.k.a Cringe Lord (Embarassment Seignour formally) spent another legendary evening indulging in an uninterrupted meme binge. Just as his spirit was about to fade into the algorithmic abyss, his tired eyes stumbled upon something unseen before—a digital relic of pure absurdity. A revelation. A prophecy in pixel form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An AI-generated image. A bird. Not just any bird—a tit with &lt;em&gt;huge&lt;/em&gt; eggs, majestically perched on a branch, as if aware of the cosmic weight it carried. The sheer audacity of its existence stunned him. This was &lt;strong&gt;it&lt;/strong&gt;. The next great artifact of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-discovery&#34;&gt;The Discovery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo Blox web framework empowers you with one of the most flexible meme-discovery and archival capabilities out there (hypothetically). But even the greatest tools could not prepare Mazursky for the sheer magnitude of his finding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A treasure hidden in the depths of AI-generated absurdity, this image was proof that machine learning had finally caught up with the internet&amp;rsquo;s most &lt;em&gt;refined&lt;/em&gt; sense of humor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mindmaps-of-madness&#34;&gt;Mindmaps of Madness&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To process the significance of this moment, Mazursky did what any self-respecting digital archivist would do—he made a mindmap. Because if an AI-generated &lt;strong&gt;tit with eggs of legend&lt;/strong&gt; deserved anything, it was structured documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using Markdown-powered mindmaps, the legendary discovery was preserved for future generations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
```markmap {height=&#34;200px&#34;}
- The Great AI Bird
  - Discovered by Cringe Lord
  - Importance
    - **Meme potential**: Unlimited
    - ~~Biological accuracy~~: Irrelevant
    - Philosophical depth: Unquantifiable
```
&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;renders as&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;markmap&#34; style=&#34;height: 200px;&#34;&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;- The Great AI Bird
  - Discovered by Cringe Lord
  - Importance
    - **Meme potential**: Unlimited
    - ~~Biological accuracy~~: Irrelevant
    - Philosophical depth: Unquantifiable&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-art-of-highlighting&#34;&gt;The Art of Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark&gt;This bird was no ordinary bird.&lt;/mark&gt; It deserved to be celebrated. To be immortalized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;mark&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Behold, the legendary bird.&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;mark&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-call-to-action&#34;&gt;A Call to Action&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/reference/markdown/#callouts&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;callouts&lt;/a&gt; to ensure the significance of this moment is not lost:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% callout note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;This AI-generated bird may change the way we perceive memes forever.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% /callout %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;renders as&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;flex px-4 py-3 mb-6 rounded-md bg-primary-100 dark:bg-primary-900&#34;&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;pr-3 pt-1 text-primary-600 dark:text-primary-300&#34;&gt;
  &lt;svg height=&#34;24&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&gt;&lt;path fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34; stroke-width=&#34;1.5&#34; d=&#34;m11.25 11.25l.041-.02a.75.75 0 0 1 1.063.852l-.708 2.836a.75.75 0 0 0 1.063.853l.041-.021M21 12a9 9 0 1 1-18 0a9 9 0 0 1 18 0m-9-3.75h.008v.008H12z&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;dark:text-neutral-300&#34;&gt;This AI-generated bird may change the way we perceive memes forever.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, if you want to make sure your audience truly understands the gravity of this moment:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;flex px-4 py-3 mb-6 rounded-md bg-yellow-100 dark:bg-yellow-900&#34;&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;pr-3 pt-1 text-red-400&#34;&gt;
  &lt;svg height=&#34;24&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&gt;&lt;path fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34; stroke-width=&#34;1.5&#34; d=&#34;M12 9v3.75m-9.303 3.376c-.866 1.5.217 3.374 1.948 3.374h14.71c1.73 0 2.813-1.874 1.948-3.374L13.949 3.378c-.866-1.5-3.032-1.5-3.898 0zM12 15.75h.007v.008H12z&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;dark:text-neutral-300&#34;&gt;This image is &lt;strong&gt;not safe&lt;/strong&gt; for weak minds unprepared for the pinnacle of AI absurdity.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-find-this-page-helpful-consider-sharing-it--or-better-yetspread-the-legend-of-the-bird-&#34;&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌 Or better yet—spread the legend of the bird! 🐦✨&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
