<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hardware | Cringe Lord</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hardware/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Hardware</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_645fa481986063ef.png</url>
      <title>Hardware</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hardware/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Your Own PC: A Journey of Hope and Regret</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/pc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;building-your-own-pc-a-journey-of-hope-and-regret&#34;&gt;Building Your Own PC: A Journey of Hope and Regret&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, you’ve decided to build your own PC? Bold move. You could have just bought a pre-built machine, but no—you&amp;rsquo;re an &lt;em&gt;engineer&lt;/em&gt;, a &lt;em&gt;technologist&lt;/em&gt;, a &lt;em&gt;visionary&lt;/em&gt;! You refuse to be scammed by overpriced &amp;ldquo;gaming&amp;rdquo; setups with RGB everything. Instead, you’ll venture into the dangerous world of DIY computer assembly, armed with only a screwdriver and a growing sense of regret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s break down the &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; process of building a PC—step by step, mistake by mistake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1-the-shopping-spree&#34;&gt;Step 1: The Shopping Spree&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, you’ll spend &lt;em&gt;weeks&lt;/em&gt; researching components, watching endless YouTube videos, and reading forum arguments about AMD vs. Intel. Eventually, you’ll settle on your parts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🧠 &lt;strong&gt;CPU&lt;/strong&gt; – The brain of your PC. Pick one that&amp;rsquo;s powerful enough but not &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; powerful, or else you’ll spend the next five years saving for a compatible GPU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🎨 &lt;strong&gt;GPU&lt;/strong&gt; – The most expensive part, because &lt;em&gt;of course&lt;/em&gt; you want to play games at ultra settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💾 &lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; – More is better, unless you enjoy watching Chrome devour your entire system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;📦 &lt;strong&gt;Motherboard&lt;/strong&gt; – Good luck picking the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; one. It must support your CPU, your RAM, your GPU, your hopes, and your dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🔌 &lt;strong&gt;Power Supply (PSU)&lt;/strong&gt; – The most overlooked part. Get a good one unless you want to &lt;em&gt;literally&lt;/em&gt; set your house on fire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💨 &lt;strong&gt;Cooling&lt;/strong&gt; – Air cooling? Liquid cooling? Stock cooler? Whatever you choose, remember: overheating is just your PC telling you it’s &lt;em&gt;too powerful&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-2-the-assembly-aka-the-panic-phase&#34;&gt;Step 2: The Assembly (a.k.a. The Panic Phase)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that you have your parts, it’s time for the fun part—putting them together! Here’s how it usually goes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Place the motherboard&lt;/strong&gt; in the case. Realize you forgot to install the I/O shield. Remove everything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install the CPU&lt;/strong&gt;. Carefully. Like, &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; carefully. Drop it once and congratulations—you now own a very expensive paperweight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply thermal paste&lt;/strong&gt;. Too little? Your CPU melts. Too much? Your entire motherboard turns into a disaster zone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install RAM&lt;/strong&gt;. Try forcing it in the wrong way for 15 minutes before realizing it only fits &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect the power cables&lt;/strong&gt;. Spend half an hour searching for where they actually go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turn it on&lt;/strong&gt;. Nothing happens. Cry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-3-the-debugging-ritual&#34;&gt;Step 3: The Debugging Ritual&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your PC refuses to turn on. Fantastic. Time for &lt;strong&gt;troubleshooting&lt;/strong&gt;, also known as &lt;em&gt;guessing until it works&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the &lt;strong&gt;RAM seated properly&lt;/strong&gt;? (Spoiler: It never is.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did you &lt;strong&gt;plug in the CPU power cable&lt;/strong&gt;? No? Fix that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there &lt;strong&gt;a rogue standoff&lt;/strong&gt; shorting your motherboard? Better hope not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you tried &lt;strong&gt;turning it off and on again&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still nothing? Welcome to the BIOS, where settings make no sense and the interface looks like it was designed in 1998.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-4-victory-or-defeat&#34;&gt;Step 4: Victory (Or Defeat)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, through sheer luck and stubbornness, your PC boots up. You let out a sigh of relief, install your OS, and finally experience the joy of a working system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least until a &lt;strong&gt;random blue screen&lt;/strong&gt; ruins your day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But hey, congratulations! You’re now part of an elite group of PC builders—those who have suffered through the process, made every mistake possible, and somehow emerged victorious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now go enjoy your &lt;em&gt;perfectly optimized&lt;/em&gt; gaming rig. Until, of course, next year, when you convince yourself you need an upgrade. 🚀💻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💡 &lt;strong&gt;Pro Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Take a picture of your perfectly built PC. It’ll remind you why you should &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; do this again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
