<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mental Issues | Cringe Lord</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mental-issues/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mental-issues/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Mental Issues</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_645fa481986063ef.png</url>
      <title>Mental Issues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mental-issues/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>🥱 Life is boring</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/bored/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/bored/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fatigue-of-doing-absolutely-nothing&#34;&gt;The Fatigue of Doing Absolutely Nothing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It happened. A historical event, a paradox, an enigma wrapped in mystery—call it what you want, but here I am, completely exhausted… from doing absolutely nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Day in, day out, I sit in my cozy cave, rarely stepping outside, except for the occasional quest to the refrigerator or the ritualistic pacing around the room while pretending to be productive. And yet, somehow, despite moving less than a houseplant, I feel drained. Physically, mentally, spiritually. Even my shadow looks disappointed in me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-science-behind-the-mystery&#34;&gt;The Science Behind the Mystery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experts would say, “You’re just mentally exhausted,” or perhaps something even more sophisticated like “prolonged sensory deprivation can lead to fatigue.” Yeah, sure. But explain to me why my biggest physical exertion this week was reaching for my phone that fell under the bed, and I still feel like I just ran a marathon—backwards, uphill, in the snow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The symptoms?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A sudden inability to focus (which, to be fair, has always been my superpower).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The feeling of wanting to do something but not knowing what (classic).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The crushing realization that I could, theoretically, go outside… but the mere thought of putting on shoes is exhausting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;solutions-that-will-probably-not-work&#34;&gt;Solutions That Will Probably Not Work&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, every self-help guru and motivational coach would have solutions:&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Take a walk.&lt;/strong&gt; (I walked to the kitchen. Didn&amp;rsquo;t help.)&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Exercise.&lt;/strong&gt; (I opened a fitness app, looked at it, then closed it. Didn&amp;rsquo;t help.)&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Meditate.&lt;/strong&gt; (I tried staring at a wall for 10 minutes. Didn&amp;rsquo;t help. Also, boring.)&lt;br&gt;
✅ &lt;strong&gt;Get some sunlight.&lt;/strong&gt; (There’s a window. That counts, right?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-inevitable-conclusion&#34;&gt;The Inevitable Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth is, doing nothing is actually really tiring. A body at rest, it turns out, does not stay at rest—it dissolves into a sluggish, existentially confused entity questioning its very purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will I recover? Probably. Will I change anything about my routine? Unlikely. But for now, I will embrace this state of paradoxical exhaustion, stare at the ceiling for an undetermined amount of time, and then, with great effort, return to my primary occupation&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
